burblesoft.com 2017-02-02

# Burble Software

Burble Software, Inc Privacy Notice

Your privacy is important to Burble Software Inc. So we've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions. 

Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.  
You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Burble Software Inc or an Burble Software Inc affiliated company. Burble Software Inc and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.  
Here are some examples of the types of personal information Burble Software Inc may collect and how we may use it. 

What personal information we collect

  * When you create a Burble Software Inc Member Account, purchase a product, download a software update, or utilize Burble Software Inc services, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information.
  * When you register for and/or participate on Burble Software Inc forums, Burble Software Inc may collect the information you provide about those people such as name, mailing address, email address, and phone number.

How we use your personal information

  * The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Burble Software Inc's latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. It also helps us to improve our services, content, and advertising. If you don't want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out at anytime by updating your preferences.
  * We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with Burble Software Inc, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.
  * We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Burble Software Inc's products, services, and customer communications.

Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where an Burble Software Inc product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.
  * We also may collect information regarding customer activities on our website, and from our other products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of the most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information, then the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

Cookies and Other Technologies

Burble Software Inc's website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. Burble Software Inc and its partners use cookies and other technologies in mobile advertising services to control the number of times you see a given ad, to deliver ads that relate to your interests, and to measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns.  
Burble Software Inc and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with Burble Software Inc more convenient and personal. Knowing someone using your computer or device has used a particular service helps us make any advertising and email communications more relevant to your interests. And knowing your contact information and information about your computer or device helps us register your products, personalize your operating system, set up your Burble Software service, and provide you with better customer service.  
As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  
We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Burble Software Inc may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.  

Disclosure to Third Parties

At times Burble Software Inc may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with Burble Software Inc to provide products and services, or that help Burble Software Inc market to customers. Personal information will only be shared by Burble Software Inc to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

Service Providers

Burble Software Inc may share personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever Burble Software Inc operates.

Others

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for Burble Software Inc to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.  
We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party. 

Protection of Personal Information

Burble Software Inc takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.  
Burble Software Inc online services use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is collected. You must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer or Safari. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it's transmitted over the Internet.  
When you use some Burble Software Inc products, services, or applications, or post on an Burble Software Inc forum or chat room, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features. 

Integrity and Retention of Personal Information

Burble Software Inc makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

Access to Personal Information

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at [https://www.BurbleSoftware.com](https://www.burblesoftware.com/). For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Burble Software Inc is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made through the regional Privacy Contact Form.

Location-Based Services

To provide location-based services on Burble Software Inc products, Burble Software Inc and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your Burble Software Inc computer or device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by Burble Software Inc and our partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based products and services. For example, we may share geographic location with application providers when you opt in to their location services, if applicable.

Third-Party Sites and Services

Burble Software Inc websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

Privacy Shield Compliance

Burble Software Company, LLC complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Burble Software Company has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Burble Software Company commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact Burble Software Company at:

  * [info@burblesoftware.com](mailto:info@burblesoftware.com) or by calling +1 734-545-8015 Burble Software Company has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints . If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint. The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.
  * As a privacy shield compliant company Burble Software is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the [Federal Trade Commission (FTC)/the Department of Transportation]
  * It is possible, under certain conditions, for the you - the individual to invoke binding arbitration

The Privacy Shield requires that, "In the context of an onward transfer, a Privacy Shield organization has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. The Privacy Shield organization shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless the organization proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage." 

Your personal data is stored by Burble Software Company to provide enrollment services so that you may sign up for activities with companies that use Burble Software to sell and manage their services.  
Example Skydive Tecumseh provides skydiving services. When you purchase a skydive through Skydive Tecumseh at [https://bookings.skydivetecumseh.com](https://bookings.skydivetecumseh.com/) Burble Software is providing the data storage and management services to support this.

You may at any point ask to be forgotten. You may contact Burble Software Company at 

  * [info@burblesoftware.com](mailto:info@burblesoftware.com) or by calling +1 734-545-8015 should you require assistance. 

Our Company-wide Commitment to Your Privacy

To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to Burble Software Inc employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

Privacy Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about Burble Software Inc's Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us.  
Burble Software Inc may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.  
Burble Software Inc, 9305 Tecumseh Clinton Hwy, Tecumseh, MI 49286

_Last updated: Jan 17, 2017_
